export const flashcards = [
  { front: "Hello", back: "Olá" },
  { front: "Goodbye", back: "Tchau" },
  { front: "Please", back: "Por favor" },
  { front: "Thank You", back: "Obrigado/Obrigada" },
  { front: "You're Welcome", back: "De Nada" },
  { front: "Yes", back: "Sim" },
  { front: "No", back: "Não" },
  { front: "Good Morning", back: "Bom Dia" },
  { front: "Good Afternoon", back: "Boa Tarde" },
  { front: "Good Evening/Night", back: "Boa Noite" },
  { front: "I Love You", back: "Eu Te Amo" },
];
